[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "``", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "''", "CC", "``", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 30, "question": "What have you unearthed of this book that is new?", "question_tokens": ["What", "have", "you", "unearthed", "of", "this", "book", "that", "is", "new", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 31, "answer": "Well, you know, when you read the Bible, you hear very spare statements like \"and they flogged him\" or \"and they crucified him.\"", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "when", "you", "read", "the", "Bible", ",", "you", "hear", "very", "spare", "statements", "like", "``", "and", "they", "flogged", "him", "''", "or", "``", "and", "they", "crucified", "him", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "Have you learned more about the kind of politics and religious corruption that led to the murder of Jesus Christ?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "learned", "more", "about", "the", "kind", "of", "politics", "and", "religious", "corruption", "that", "led", "to", "the", "murder", "of", "Jesus", "Christ", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 50, "question": "What is your response to that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "response", "to", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 51, "answer": "Well, it's not at all anti-Semitic.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "not", "at", "all", "anti-Semitic", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 61, "question": "In terms of the mythology around the death of Jesus Christ, what would you say now is definitely myth and what is indisputable pretty well widely agreed fact about what happened?", "question_tokens": ["In", "terms", "of", "the", "mythology", "around", "the", "death", "of", "Jesus", "Christ", ",", "what", "would", "you", "say", "now", "is", "definitely", "myth", "and", "what", "is", "indisputable", "pretty", "well", "widely", "agreed", "fact", "about", "what", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "RB", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 62, "answer": "Well, there's no question there was a Jesus.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "'s", "no", "question", "there", "was", "a", "Jesus", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Sunday"]}, "docId": "130329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "DT", "VBP", "RB", ":", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 76, "question": "What do you think was built up that is just not true?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "was", "built", "up", "that", "is", "just", "not", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBD", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 77, "answer": "Well, I think a lot of the sort of Sunday school, if I may say it that way, images about the cross, the crucifixion, sometimes these are almost -- almost placid in their presentation, a calm Jesus hanging on the cross.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "a", "lot", "of", "the", "sort", "of", "Sunday", "school", ",", "if", "I", "may", "say", "it", "that", "way", ",", "images", "about", "the", "cross", ",", "the", "crucifixion", ",", "sometimes", "these", "are", "almost", "--", "almost", "placid", "in", "their", "presentation", ",", "a", "calm", "Jesus", "hanging", "on", "the", "cross", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 90, "question": "Do you think there is now irrefutable evidence from a scholastic point of view that it does date to at least the time when Jesus was alive?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "there", "is", "now", "irrefutable", "evidence", "from", "a", "scholastic", "point", "of", "view", "that", "it", "does", "date", "to", "at", "least", "the", "time", "when", "Jesus", "was", "alive", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "TO", "IN", "JJS", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "NNP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "Well, you have been very kind to me in calling me a scholar.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "have", "been", "very", "kind", "to", "me", "in", "calling", "me", "a", "scholar", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 126, "question": "What is it like being called the pastor-in-chief to the president of the United States?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "it", "like", "being", "called", "the", "pastor-in-chief", "to", "the", "president", "of", "the", "United", "States", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "aSentId": 127, "answer": "Well, you know, it's been an honor to work for this president.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "it", "'s", "been", "an", "honor", "to", "work", "for", "this", "president", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["United States"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Second Corinthians"]}, "docId": "130329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "WRB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", ",", "CC", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 143, "question": "Well, what do you say to the president at a time like that?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "what", "do", "you", "say", "to", "the", "president", "at", "a", "time", "like", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 144, "answer": "You know, we spent a lot of time mediating on Scripture, Second Corinthians, where it talks about how outwardly, we are wasting away, but inwardly, we are being renewed day by day because our light and momentary troubles are leading to something better.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "we", "spent", "a", "lot", "of", "time", "mediating", "on", "Scripture", ",", "Second", "Corinthians", ",", "where", "it", "talks", "about", "how", "outwardly", ",", "we", "are", "wasting", "away", ",", "but", "inwardly", ",", "we", "are", "being", "renewed", "day", "by", "day", "because", "our", "light", "and", "momentary", "troubles", "are", "leading", "to", "something", "better", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 160, "question": "What do you say, as a pastor that has to talk to people who may be confused about this, what do you say about the evolution, I guess, of gay rights and gay marriage in America?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "say", ",", "as", "a", "pastor", "that", "has", "to", "talk", "to", "people", "who", "may", "be", "confused", "about", "this", ",", "what", "do", "you", "say", "about", "the", "evolution", ",", "I", "guess", ",", "of", "gay", "rights", "and", "gay", "marriage", "in", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "TO", "NNS", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 161, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 183, "question": "What do you make of what is going on here?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "what", "is", "going", "on", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 184, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 211, "question": "And what is the kind of thing you used to e-mail him which really moved him?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "is", "the", "kind", "of", "thing", "you", "used", "to", "e-mail", "him", "which", "really", "moved", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 212, "answer": "Sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 222, "question": "And if there was one Scripture that you could use or one extract from a Scripture that you would send to any would-be president, which one would you choose?", "question_tokens": ["And", "if", "there", "was", "one", "Scripture", "that", "you", "could", "use", "or", "one", "extract", "from", "a", "Scripture", "that", "you", "would", "send", "to", "any", "would-be", "president", ",", "which", "one", "would", "you", "choose", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "CD", "NNP", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CC", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WDT", "CD", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 223, "answer": "That's a great question, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "a", "great", "question", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Rahm"]}, "docId": "130329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 256, "question": "As the older, the eldest sibling, what was your reaction to that treachery?", "question_tokens": ["As", "the", "older", ",", "the", "eldest", "sibling", ",", "what", "was", "your", "reaction", "to", "that", "treachery", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJS", "VBG", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 257, "answer": "Oh, well, Rahm is, you know, you've heard of sibling rivalry.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "well", ",", "Rahm", "is", ",", "you", "know", ",", "you", "'ve", "heard", "of", "sibling", "rivalry", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Emanuel"]}, "docId": "130329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "JJ", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "JJ", ",", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 264, "question": "When you look back over your early childhood together, what was it, do you think, about the environment and atmosphere of the Emanuel household that drove you guys to be so successful?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "look", "back", "over", "your", "early", "childhood", "together", ",", "what", "was", "it", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "about", "the", "environment", "and", "atmosphere", "of", "the", "Emanuel", "household", "that", "drove", "you", "guys", "to", "be", "so", "successful", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 265, "answer": "So, first, let me make clear that when we had graduated from high school, there is no one who would have said, oh, those Emanuel boys, they're destined to succeed.", "answer_tokens": ["So", ",", "first", ",", "let", "me", "make", "clear", "that", "when", "we", "had", "graduated", "from", "high", "school", ",", "there", "is", "no", "one", "who", "would", "have", "said", ",", "oh", ",", "those", "Emanuel", "boys", ",", "they", "'re", "destined", "to", "succeed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "VBD", "RB", "VB", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 281, "question": "Basically, Ari's behavior ever since, it's down to you two, isn't it, tormenting him in that bunk bed?", "question_tokens": ["Basically", ",", "Ari", "'s", "behavior", "ever", "since", ",", "it", "'s", "down", "to", "you", "two", ",", "is", "n't", "it", ",", "tormenting", "him", "in", "that", "bunk", "bed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "TO", "PRP", "CD", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 282, "answer": "Yes, but once you don't -- didn't read, Piers, is that he really enjoyed that and --", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "but", "once", "you", "do", "n't", "--", "did", "n't", "read", ",", "Piers", ",", "is", "that", "he", "really", "enjoyed", "that", "and", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ari"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 288, "question": "And despite all the rivalry, you're actually very loyal to each other, aren't you?", "question_tokens": ["And", "despite", "all", "the", "rivalry", ",", "you", "'re", "actually", "very", "loyal", "to", "each", "other", ",", "are", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 289, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 304, "question": "What was all that about?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "all", "that", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "DT", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 305, "answer": "Well, I -- it's not about the book, but it's about the fact that, uh, whatever.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "--", "it", "'s", "not", "about", "the", "book", ",", "but", "it", "'s", "about", "the", "fact", "that", ",", "uh", ",", "whatever", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 334, "question": "Did they take the Ari golden corn tamale off the menu?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "they", "take", "the", "Ari", "golden", "corn", "tamale", "off", "the", "menu", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 335, "answer": "No, it's still there.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "it", "'s", "still", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ari"]}, "docId": "130329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "NN", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 351, "question": "Does it sound like the kind of brother you've come to know and love, the one you used to torment in his bunk bed?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "it", "sound", "like", "the", "kind", "of", "brother", "you", "'ve", "come", "to", "know", "and", "love", ",", "the", "one", "you", "used", "to", "torment", "in", "his", "bunk", "bed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", ",", "DT", "CD", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 352, "answer": "Well, I think -- look, Ari is a lovely person.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "--", "look", ",", "Ari", "is", "a", "lovely", "person", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "-- who is the single most impressive celebrity or famous public figure you ever met in your life who you would sign up if you were running a talent agency?", "question_tokens": ["--", "who", "is", "the", "single", "most", "impressive", "celebrity", "or", "famous", "public", "figure", "you", "ever", "met", "in", "your", "life", "who", "you", "would", "sign", "up", "if", "you", "were", "running", "a", "talent", "agency", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "I've met a lot of famous and, I think, very impressive people.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "met", "a", "lot", "of", "famous", "and", ",", "I", "think", ",", "very", "impressive", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 387, "question": "And if you were White House chief of staff, what is the single most important policy you would, if you had complete power, encourage a president to bring in to improve America?", "question_tokens": ["And", "if", "you", "were", "White", "House", "chief", "of", "staff", ",", "what", "is", "the", "single", "most", "important", "policy", "you", "would", ",", "if", "you", "had", "complete", "power", ",", "encourage", "a", "president", "to", "bring", "in", "to", "improve", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 388, "answer": "Well, at that moment, I have -- I'm in health care.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "at", "that", "moment", ",", "I", "have", "--", "I", "'m", "in", "health", "care", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 425, "question": "-- what are you thinking?", "question_tokens": ["--", "what", "are", "you", "thinking", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 426, "answer": "Whoo.", "answer_tokens": ["Whoo", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 430, "question": "Are you surprised at the speed of your ascent?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "surprised", "at", "the", "speed", "of", "your", "ascent", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 431, "answer": "It depends.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "depends", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "130329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "RB", ",", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "America, I would imagine, remains the holy grail for all singer-songwriters, in the end, doesn't it?", "question_tokens": ["America", ",", "I", "would", "imagine", ",", "remains", "the", "holy", "grail", "for", "all", "singer-songwriters", ",", "in", "the", "end", ",", "does", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "I'm -- I'm still surprised I'm like on single (INAUDIBLE), like I have the opportunity to release singles here, um, for English musicians, America is always an untouchable thing.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "--", "I", "'m", "still", "surprised", "I", "'m", "like", "on", "single", "(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", ",", "like", "I", "have", "the", "opportunity", "to", "release", "singles", "here", ",", "um", ",", "for", "English", "musicians", ",", "America", "is", "always", "an", "untouchable", "thing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 445, "question": "Anything you want to get off your chest?", "question_tokens": ["Anything", "you", "want", "to", "get", "off", "your", "chest", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 446, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 449, "question": "No truth to the rumor I'm just about to invent that she dumped Harry Stiles for you?", "question_tokens": ["No", "truth", "to", "the", "rumor", "I", "'m", "just", "about", "to", "invent", "that", "she", "dumped", "Harry", "Stiles", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "TO", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "No, I think --", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "think", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Harry Stiles"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "JJS", ",", "WRB", "DT", ":", "WRB", ":", "WRB", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "RP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "JJS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "WRB", ":", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 451, "question": "The better looking, extra member of One Direction?", "question_tokens": ["The", "better", "looking", ",", "extra", "member", "of", "One", "Direction", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJR", "VBG", ",", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 452, "answer": "To be honest, when that -- when -- when that rumor came out, it kind of felt like a bit of -- a bit of lazy journalism, to be honest, because I think people when -- whenever she's pictured with someone, people will say that she's dating them, whoever they are.", "answer_tokens": ["To", "be", "honest", ",", "when", "that", "--", "when", "--", "when", "that", "rumor", "came", "out", ",", "it", "kind", "of", "felt", "like", "a", "bit", "of", "--", "a", "bit", "of", "lazy", "journalism", ",", "to", "be", "honest", ",", "because", "I", "think", "people", "when", "--", "whenever", "she", "'s", "pictured", "with", "someone", ",", "people", "will", "say", "that", "she", "'s", "dating", "them", ",", "whoever", "they", "are", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WP", ":", "WP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "IN", "CD", "CC", "CD", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "How can you be so sure that as your fame continues, the money continues, et cetera, you won't fall prey to a very familiar rocky path?", "question_tokens": ["How", "can", "you", "be", "so", "sure", "that", "as", "your", "fame", "continues", ",", "the", "money", "continues", ",", "et", "cetera", ",", "you", "wo", "n't", "fall", "prey", "to", "a", "very", "familiar", "rocky", "path", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "TO", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "I -- as you know, in the industry, you meet a lot of people who -- who are fond of drugs and they're -- it really -- I met a lot of them when I was quite young, like 16 or 17, and it really just put me off.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "as", "you", "know", ",", "in", "the", "industry", ",", "you", "meet", "a", "lot", "of", "people", "who", "--", "who", "are", "fond", "of", "drugs", "and", "they", "'re", "--", "it", "really", "--", "I", "met", "a", "lot", "of", "them", "when", "I", "was", "quite", "young", ",", "like", "16", "or", "17", ",", "and", "it", "really", "just", "put", "me", "off", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 475, "question": "Seriously?", "question_tokens": ["Seriously", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 476, "answer": "-- a bit odd.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "a", "bit", "odd", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 481, "question": "What do you feel when you see that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "feel", "when", "you", "see", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 482, "answer": "I think it's sad.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "sad", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 483, "question": "I think it's -- I think it's sad that there weren't more people telling her that, to be honest, because you could say that to her, but is she necessarily going to listen to you?", "question_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "--", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "sad", "that", "there", "were", "n't", "more", "people", "telling", "her", "that", ",", "to", "be", "honest", ",", "because", "you", "could", "say", "that", "to", "her", ",", "but", "is", "she", "necessarily", "going", "to", "listen", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "RB", "RBR", "NNS", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", ",", "TO", "VB", "JJS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "TO", "PRP$", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 484, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "You write most of your music or all of it?", "question_tokens": ["You", "write", "most", "of", "your", "music", "or", "all", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "I'd say, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'d", "say", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 499, "question": "Where do you get the inspiration for this stuff?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "do", "you", "get", "the", "inspiration", "for", "this", "stuff", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 500, "answer": "I'm influenced by a lot of things.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "influenced", "by", "a", "lot", "of", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "JJS", "."], "qSentId": 502, "question": "Who's your hero?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "'s", "your", "hero", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 503, "answer": "Probably my dad, to be honest.", "answer_tokens": ["Probably", "my", "dad", ",", "to", "be", "honest", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 505, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 506, "answer": "Because he got me into all of that stuff.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "he", "got", "me", "into", "all", "of", "that", "stuff", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Van Morrison"]}, "docId": "130329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNPS", "NN", "VBN", "``", "JJ", "NNP", ",", "''", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", ":"], "qSentId": 509, "question": "ORGAN: And if I took you to a desert island and left you there and you could have one album, not yours, to listen to the rest of your life, what would you have?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "And", "if", "I", "took", "you", "to", "a", "desert", "island", "and", "left", "you", "there", "and", "you", "could", "have", "one", "album", ",", "not", "yours", ",", "to", "listen", "to", "the", "rest", "of", "your", "life", ",", "what", "would", "you", "have", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NN", ",", "RB", "NNS", ",", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "Really, Van Morrison and the Chieftains album called \"Irish Heartbeat,\" because that -- that was the first --", "answer_tokens": ["Really", ",", "Van", "Morrison", "and", "the", "Chieftains", "album", "called", "``", "Irish", "Heartbeat", ",", "''", "because", "that", "--", "that", "was", "the", "first", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 514, "question": "And if you could take one woman to the desert island to listen to the music with, who would that be?", "question_tokens": ["And", "if", "you", "could", "take", "one", "woman", "to", "the", "desert", "island", "to", "listen", "to", "the", "music", "with", ",", "who", "would", "that", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "WP", "MD", "IN", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 515, "answer": "Uh --", "answer_tokens": ["Uh", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]